{
    "id": "23c66923ea6f4fe5819a3312a9b4c19e",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Manchester is known ……………….. its textile industry.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "of",
                "about"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d3f6c2ca704049ea9f16294b56da4fd2"
        },
        {
            "question": "The goat subsists ………………… leaves.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "on",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2b58ff41504841bd8ba91b38de7b4727"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is quite fond ………………. her grandchildren.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "off",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9bc8d54dbfc64806a91800420126b008"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is natural for men to wish ………………. distinction.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "about",
                "at",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "9f1d5bd75474414f943f3702c9d6d996"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is evident that he is enamored ………………… her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "of",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "40c82ada5dc443418038137e5db17b60"
        },
        {
            "question": "Ambition does not always conduce ………………. happiness.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "to",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0e8be46037804e1c92a1dd4a880e53cf"
        },
        {
            "question": "Nowadays computers are cheap enough to be accessible ………………… most people.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ae61634f861944f88b46729c6ff0817e"
        },
        {
            "question": "A gentleman is courteous ……………… his neighbors.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "with",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "eef6a5c6c87b4713970b4b6a863f3a6b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am indebted ………………. you for your help.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "to",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4c58e923905c4c7bbce30956e531df9d"
        },
        {
            "question": "People who are averse ……………….. hard work do not succeed in life.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "with",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "0d284e48daf644c5aa3730bcf70e682f"
        },
        {
            "question": "There is no cure ………………. the common cold.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "with",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "29765f2a03584e1ba2a72f92540b5555"
        },
        {
            "question": "The noise from upstairs prevented me ………………… sleeping.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "with",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9cedc2aa76f84494bdb7e721f629f393"
        }
    ]
}